# Regina Nigmatullina

# Senior Front End Developer

Bali, Indonesia & Dubai, UAE | +62 812 3 999 35 02, +7 (917) 453-12-67 (WhatsApp) | nigmatullinaregina@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/reginanigmatullina/ 3 regina-nigma.com/



#### Summary

I'm professional Front-End Developer with 11 years of extensive experience.

I have commercial development experience using Angular, AngularJS, React, Vue3, Ionic, React Native. Proficient in JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML5, CSS3, SASS, and LESS. I have a deep understanding of web development tools and practices.

Having worked in Agile teams, I bring a collaborative and adaptive approach to my work. I'm quick to identify and resolve bugs, both in Javascript and Typescript, and has pixel-perfect accuracy when defining and implementing front-end experiences.

My goal is to provide clean usable interfaces and develop the most flexible and efficient application.

# Work experience

# Lead Front End Developer

October 2018 - October 2023

#### Similie

- I took on a leading role within the company and demonstrated a meticulous, actionoriented approach.
- Achieved a complete Parabl front-end redesign, tackling legacy code.
- Implemented BEM methodology for organized UI components.
- Introduced dynamic theming for personalized user experiences (light and dark modes).
- Performed code reviews and code quality of styles system.

### Front End Developer

January 2019 - October 2019

#### Codersclan

- I was responsible for implementing WordPress templates that not only met the aesthetic requirements of clients but were also highly responsive.
- Created a custom Eurovision 2019 sponsor Wordpress template.
- I also had the privilege of developing a mobile application for a game using Cordova.

#### Front End Developer

March 2018 - August 2018

#### **Payever**

- Worked on complex applications using Angular 6.
- Performed code reviews and code quality of styles system.
- Developed UI components based on own ui-kit system, delivering the best UX to customers.
- Created solutions using own bootstrapping system to code with.

# Front End Developer

July 2016 - March 2018

#### **Brobotics**

- Developed one-page applications using Angular 2/4 (Typescript).
- Organized styles system using BEM methodology (well organized UI components).
- Developed mobile application using Ionic.
- Automated Unit Tests (Jasmine, Karma) to verify the applications' workflows and to guarantee the delivery of high-quality code.

#### Web Developer

June 2012 - July 2016

#### Kiweb

 Developed websites using HTML, CSS, jQuery, Javascript and CMS (Joomla, Wordpress, Drupal, etc).

#### **Skills**

- Angular / AngularJS
- React
- Vue3
- Strong knowledge of native JavaScript
- Typescript
- HTML5 / CSS3 / SASS / LESS
- Pixel Perfect Development
- Wordpress
- Mobile development using Cordova and Ionic
- Mobile development using React Native
- Gulp
- Git
- Jasmine, Karma, Jest
- Bootstrap 3, 4, 5
- OOP
- NPM
- BEM methodology

#### **Education**

2011-2015

Ufa State Aviation Technical University

Bachelor of Mathematical Software and Information Systems Administration